// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many seasons of Grey's Anatomy are there?",
    answer: "18 and counting",
    options: [
      "12",
      "18 and counting",
      "20",
      "15"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When did Grey's Anatomy start?",
    answer: "2005",
    options: [
      "2004",
      "2005",
      "2006",
      "2007"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What season is the musical episode in?",
    answer: "Season seven",
    options: [
      "Season nine",
      "Season six",
      "Season seven",
      "Season eight"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What color scrubs do interns wear? What about attendings?",
    answer: "Light blue for interns, dark blue for attendings",
    options: [
      "Blue for interns, grey for attendings",
      "Light blue for interns, dark blue for attendings",
      "Light green for interns, dark green for attendings",
      "Pink for interns, Orange for attendings"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is Derek's signature saying?",
    answer: "It's a beautiful day to save lives. Let's have some fun",
    options: [
      "I'm McDreamy",
      "This isn't right. You should have taken me to get a head CT",
      "It's a beautiful day to save lives",
      "It's a beautiful day to save lives. Let's have some fun"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "As of season 18, how many original cast members are still on the show?",
    answer: "Three: Meredith, Bailey, Webber",
    options: [
      "Six: Meredith, Karev, Avery, Kepner, Bailey, Webber",
      "Five: Meredith, Karev, Avery, Bailey, Webber",
      "Four: Merdith, Avery, Bailey, Webber",
      "Three: Meredith, Bailey, Webber"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who are Meredith's first roommates?",
    answer: "Izzie and George",
    options: [
      "Izzie and George",
      "Cristina, Izzie and George",
      "Izzie, George and Alex",
      "Cristina, Izzie, George and Alex"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these is not a character nickname?",
    answer: "McDoctor",
    options: [
      "007",
      "Medusa",
      "The Nazi",
      "McDoctor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of these characters started out as enemies?",
    answer: "Meredith and Alex",
    options: [
      "Meredith and Alex",
      "Addison and Bailey",
      "Webber and Ellis",
      "George and Burke"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of these characters had the most memorable introduction?",
    answer: "Addison Montgomery",
    options: [
      "Lexie Grey",
      "Addison Montgomery",
      "Catherine Avery",
      "Mark Sloan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of these was the shortest marraige?",
    answer: "Meredith and Alex",
    options: [
      "Alex and Izzie",
      "Cristina and Owen",
      "George and Callie",
      "Owen and Amelia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What was Meredith's dog's name?",
    answer: "Doc",
    options: [
      "Finn",
      "Bingo",
      "Doc",
      "Shepherd"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "How many sisters does Derek have?",
    answer: "Four",
    options: [
      "Four",
      "Three",
      "Five",
      "Six"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which is the best hospital name?",
    answer: "Seattle Grace Mercy Death",
    options: [
      "Seattle Grace Mercy West",
      "Seattle Grace",
      "Grey Sloan Memorial",
      "Seattle Grace Mercy Death"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Why does Izzie see visions of Denny Duquette?",
    answer: "She had a brain tumor",
    options: [
      "She felt guilty for cutting his LVAD wire",
      "She missed him so much",
      "Because he left her a lot of money",
      "She had a brain tumor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Where does Derek propose to Meredith?",
    answer: "In the elevator",
    options: [
      "In the locker room with a post it",
      "At Meredith's field of candles",
      "At Derek's Trailer",
      "In the elevator"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What unusual color is Cristina's wedding dress in season 7?",
    answer: "Red",
    options: [
      "Red",
      "Black",
      "Purple",
      "Brown"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which doctors are in the plane crash?",
    answer: "Meredith and Alex",
    options: [
      "Meredith, Alex, Derek, Mark, Lexie, and Arizona",
      "Meredith, Cristina, Derek, Mark, Lexie, and Callie",
      "Meredith, Cristina, Mark, Lexie, and Arizona.",
      "Meredith, Cristina, Derek, Mark, Lexie, and Arizona."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Who is Ada's favorite character?",
    answer: "Lexie Grey",
    options: [
      "Lexie Grey",
      "Alex Karev",
      "Miranda Bailey",
      "Cristina Yang"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which character death was the most painful?",
    answer: "Derek Shepherd",
    options: [
      "Mark Sloan",
      "George O'Malley",
      "Lexie Grey",
      "Derek Shepherd"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Which was the best teacher-student duo?",
    answer: "Plastics: Mark Sloan and Jackson Avery",
    options: [
      "Plastics: Mark Sloan and Jackson Avery",
      "Pediatrics: Arizona Robbins and Alex Karev",
      "Cardio: Teddy Altman and Cristina Yang",
      "General: Richard Webber and Meredith Grey"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "When did Grey's become uninteresting?",
    answer: "After Derek Shepherd died",
    options: [
      "After the shooting",
      "After the plane crash",
      "After Cristina Yang left",
      "After Derek Shepherd died"
    ]
  },
];